Guide to the Records of the Women's Philharmonic M1470
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series XII: Composer biographical material
  - Individual Composers
    - Dobbins, Lori (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Dong, kui (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Du Page, Florence (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Eckhardt-Gramatte, S.C. (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Eiridsdottir, Karolina (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Ekizian, Michelle (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Elsea, Veronica (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Epstein, Marti (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Erisman, Zoe (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Escot, Pozzi (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Evan-Or, Mary (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Garrop, Stacy (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Guidetti, Pamela (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Higdon, Jennifer (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Hong, Gao (Box 165, Folder 4)
    - Hoover, Katherine (Box 165, Folder 5)
    - Hyde, Robyn: Resume (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Jean Renaud, Joan (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Karpman, Laura (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Kats-Cherin, Elena (Box 165, Folder 6)
    - Krinitsky, Ann (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Le Fanu, Nicola (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Le Baron, Anne (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - La Barbara, Joan (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Lackman, Susan Cohn (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Lam, Bun-Ching (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Lamb, Sally (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Lann, Vanessa (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Larsen, Libby (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Larsen, Libby (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Larsen, Libby (Box 165, Folder 7)
    - Lauer, Elizabeth (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Lebenbom, Elaine F. (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Leon, Tania (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Luo, Jing-Jing (Haven) (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Loudova, Ivana (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Lomon, Ruth (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Llewellyn, Becky (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Linden, Camm (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Lind, Lanette (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Lim, Liza (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Leseige, Annette (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Lee, I-Chunn (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Lee, Hope (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Lockhart, Beatriz (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Marcus, Bonita (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Mamlok, Ursula (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Mamlof-Forssling, Carin (Box 112, Folder 35)
    - Memdieta, Ana (Box 112, Folder 36)
    - Mercer, Janis (Box 112, Folder 37)
    - Merrell, Ann (Box 112, Folder 38)
    - Maricle, Sherrie (Box 112, Folder 39)
    - Marshall, Pamela (Box 112, Folder 40)
    - Martin, Delores (Box 112, Folder 41)
    - Martin, Judith (Box 112, Folder 42)
    - Mayer, Margaret (Box 112, Folder 43)
    - Mazourova, Jarmila (Box 112, Folder 44)
    - McIntosh, Diana (Box 112, Folder 45)
    - McLean, Priscella (Box 112, Folder 46)
    - McTee, Cindy (Box 112, Folder 47)
    - von Maack, Hazel (Box 112, Folder 48)
    - Maconchy, Elizabeth (Box 112, Folder 49)
    - Mageau, Mary (Box 112, Folder 50)
    - McBride, Melissa (Box 112, Folder 51)
    - Maguire, Janet (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Mahler, Alma (Schindler) (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Mekeel, Joyce (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Meier, Margaret (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Merryman, Marjorie (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Myers, Amina C. (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Murray, Diedre (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Munn, Zae (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Mundy, Nancy (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Michelson, Helena (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Montano, Linda (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Moore, Mary Carr (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Muhl, Erika (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Musgrave, Thea (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Na, Hyo-shim (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Nan, Sheli (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Newmar, Marylou (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Nez, Ketty (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Niederberger, Maria (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Nordmann, Corinne T. (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Oblak, Jerica (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - O'Brien, Joy Ellen (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - O'Connell, Katherine (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Olivero, Betty (Box 113, Folder 22)
    - Oliveros, Pauline (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - Oppens, Ursula (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Ore,Cecilie (Box 113, Folder 24)
    - Ortiz, Gabriella (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Osterman, Eurydice (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - Oswald, Rebecca (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Oswald, Rebecca (Box 113, Folder 26)
    - Owen, Julie K. (Box 113, Folder 27)
    - Owen, Morfydd (Box 113, Folder 28)
    - Oyens, Tera de Marez (Box 113, Folder 29)
    - Pagh-Paan, Younghi (Box 113, Folder 30)
    - Papadakos, Dorothy (Box 113, Folder 31)
    - Paradis, Maria Theresa von (Box 113, Folder 32)
    - Paredes, Hilda (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - Parker, Alice (Box 113, Folder 34)
    - Peachey, Janet (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - Pejacevic, Dora (Box 113, Folder 36)
    - Pentland, Barbara (Box 113, Folder 37)
    - Perry, Linda (Box 113, Folder 38)
    - Petrova, Elena (Box 113, Folder 39)
    - Pierce, Alexander (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Pirello, Concetta (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Pizer, Elizabeth (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Price, Deon Nielson (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Price, Florence (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Prieto, Maria Teresa (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Ptaszynska, Marta (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Procaccini, Teresa (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - Radoje, Maria (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Radunskaya, Ami (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Ran, Shulamit (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Ran, Shulamit (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Reed, Nancy Binns (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Reese, Mona Lyn (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Reich, Amy (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Reid, Wendy (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Reynolds, Belinda (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Richter, Marga (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Robert-George, Eliane (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - Rodriguez, Marcela (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Roosa, Alissa (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Rosco, B. J. (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Rubin, Amy (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Rubin, Anna (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Rud, Diana Elena (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - Rudlow, Vivian Adelberg (Box 154, Folder 24)
    - Ruehr, Elena (Box 154, Folder 25)
    - Rusche, Marjorie (Box 154, Folder 26)
    - Rycenga, Jennifer (Box 154, Folder 27)
    - Saariaho, Kaija (Box 154, Folder 28)
    - St. John, Kathleen (Box 154, Folder 29)
    - Sainte Crox, Judith (Box 154, Folder 30)
    - Sams, Carol (Box 154, Folder 31)
    - Samter, Alice (Box 154, Folder 32)
    - Samuel, Virginia (Box 154, Folder 33)
    - Sandler, Felicia (Box 154, Folder 34)
    - Sato, Sumiko (Box 154, Folder 35)
    - Scherchen-Hsiag, Tona (Box 154, Folder 36)
    - Schieve, Catherine (Box 154, Folder 37)
    - Schmidt, Heather (Box 154, Folder 38)
    - Schonfeld, Lori (Box 154, Folder 39)
    - Schonthal, Ruth (Box 154, Folder 40)
    - Schrag, Molly (Box 154, Folder 41)
    - Schramm, Betsy (Box 154, Folder 42)
    - Schumann, Clara (Box 154, Folder 43)
    - Schumann, Laura E. (Box 154, Folder 44)
    - Schwartz, Anne (Box 154, Folder 45)
    - Schwendinger, Laura (Box 154, Folder 46)
    - Seeger, Ruth C. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Seltzer, Linda (Box 154, Folder 47)
    - Shaffer, Jeanne (Box 154, Folder 48)
    - Shatin, Judith (Box 154, Folder 49)
    - Shlonsky, Verdina (Box 154, Folder 50)
    - Shore, Clare (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Shrude, Marilyn (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Shubinskaya, Valentina (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Sikora, Elzbieta (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Silsbee, Ann (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Silver, Sheila (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Silver, Sheila (Box 165, Folder 8)
    - Silverman, Faye-Ellen (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Simons, Netty (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Smyth, Dame Ethel (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Snyder, Amy (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Son, Yung Wha (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Southam, Ann (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Speach, Bernadette (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Sprecher, Sandra (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Steinberg, Carolyn (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Stiles, Mary (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Stone, Elaine M. (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Sutherland, Margaret (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Swados, Elizabeth (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - Swedensky, Linda (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Swisher, Gloria (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - Tailleferre, Germaine (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Takahashi, Yoko (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - Tann, Hilary (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Tan, Su Lian (Box 155, Folder 25)
    - Tanaka, Karen (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Tate, Phyllis (Box 155, Folder 26)
    - Telfer, Nancy (Box 155, Folder 27)
    - Terzian, Alicia (Box 155, Folder 28)
    - Themen, Irana (Box 155, Folder 29)
    - Thomas, Augusta Reed (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Thomas, Karen P. (Box 155, Folder 30)
    - Thomas, Marily Taft (Box 155, Folder 31)
    - Thome, Diane (Box 155, Folder 32)
    - Thorington, Helen (Box 155, Folder 33)
    - Thorkelsdottir, Mist (Box 155, Folder 34)
    - Torikai, Ushio (Box 155, Folder 35)
    - Tower, Joan (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Urner, Catherine (Box 155, Folder 36)
    - Ustvolskaya, Galina (Box 155, Folder 37)
    - Vamos, Grace (Box 155, Folder 38)
    - Van Appledorn, Mary-Jean (Box 155, Folder 39)
    - Vandervelde, Janika (Box 155, Folder 40)
    - Van de Vate, Nancy (Box 155, Folder 41)
    - Varga, Balint Andras (Box 155, Folder 42)
    - Vehar, Persis (Box 155, Folder 43)
    - Vellere, Lucie (Box 155, Folder 44)
    - Vercoe, Elizabeth (Box 155, Folder 45)
    - Vierk, Lois (Box 155, Folder 46)
    - Villanueva, Mariana (Box 155, Folder 47)
    - Vogelsong, Kirsten (Box 155, Folder 48)
    - Vorlava, Slava (Box 155, Folder 49)
    - Wachsman, Dianne (Box 155, Folder 50)
    - Wallach, Joelle (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Walker, Gwyneth (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Walker, Gwyneth (Box 165, Folder 9)
    - Wang, An-ming (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Warren, Elinor Remick (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Warshaw, Dalit (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Warshauer, Maxine (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Watkins, Mary (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Weesner, Anna (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Weigl, Valerie (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Weir, Judith (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Wendt, Donnalynn (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Whitehead, Gillian (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Whitfield, Nadine (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Wiemann, Beth (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Wilkins, Margaret Lucy (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - Williams, Amy (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Wilson, Janis Dunson (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - Wishart, Betty R. (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Wolfe, Julia (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - Wood, Margaret (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Yang, Fengshi (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - Yarnell, Carolyn (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Zaidel-Rudolph, Jeanne (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - Zaimont, Judith Lang (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - Zechlin, Ruth (Box 156, Folder 25)
    - Zen, Gabriela (Box 156, Folder 26)
    - Zhou, Long (Box 156, Folder 27)
    - Zielinska, Lidia (Box 156, Folder 28)
    - Ziffrin, Marilyn J. (Box 156, Folder 29)
    - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe (Box 156, Folder 30)
    - Zwilich, Ellen Taaffe (Box 165, Folder 10)
  - Artists/Composers Miscellaneous
    - Mendelssohn and Boulanger: copyright and correspondence materials (Box 165, Folder 11)
    - Chamber Music by women composers, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 12)
    - Misc. press releases and materials, 1997-2000 (Box 165, Folder 13)
    - Misc. Concert Press and Reviews (Box 165, Folder 14)
    - Active players address/phone list, 1999 (Box 165, Folder 15)
    - Orchestra members, 1999 (Box 165, Folder 16)
    - Orchestra members, 2000 (Box 165, Folder 17)
    - Historic female composers materials (Box 165, Folder 18)
    - Artist relations (Box 165, Folder 19)
    - Hotels (Box 165, Folder 20)
    - Artist bios (Box 165, Folder 21)
    - Jennifer Higdon, correspondence (Box 165, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence re. Florence Price concert (Box 165, Folder 23)
    - Orchestra Players Committee, 1995 (Box 165, Folder 24)
    - Composer Addresses (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Composer Bios (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Women Composers on Disk (floppy disks) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - YB Composer Research (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Artist Correspondence (2000 - 2001) (Box 104, Folder 14)
- Series XIII: Music Library Materials
  Music Library Materials
  This includes: correspondence regarding rental and perusal loans; publisher resources and guides featuring the works of women composers; selected repertoire lists; music preparation guidelines and miscellaneous music library correspondence. Also included are: sample repertoire lists; timing lists of various pieces; research notes on women composers; publisher invoices; part assignment lists and bowing notations for selected repertoire.
  - Music Preparation Guidelines (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - 3 Scores (no titles/no composer) (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Music Library Correspondance 1999-00 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Out on Perusal: Loaned Scores to other organizations (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Music Publishers, misc. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Perusal Orders 1998-99 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - ASCAP License Duties (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rental Requests; 2000 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Selected Repertoire Lists by Women Composers (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Music library correspondance; music part assignments (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Feb, 26, 2000 - set 2- library notes (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Reference Materials; Women Composers (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Reference Materials; Women Composers (2) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Music Library/ Orchestra Librarian (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Music Score Rentals (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Blanks-rentals (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Top Ten" Repertoire (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Tape Library and Archival Tape Loans (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Orchestral Rep. Timings - Fogel Record Library (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Timings for Chamber + Recital Repertoire-Fogel Records (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Latin American Composers (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Women Composers/Lists Publishers (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Rentals--scores lists (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Baroque repertoire list (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Womens Composers Mock Up Catalog (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Music on loan forms (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Music Rental inquiries (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Music Rentals list (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - "Gerald McBoing Boing" Score (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Request forms (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Composer/Piece Performance History (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Music Rentals (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Rental Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Library (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Music on Loan Form (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Rental-General (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Rentals Pending-check weekly (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - March 4, 1999 Mendelsshon Rentals (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Works performed by the Women's Phil. (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - 1992 Publisher perusal returns (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - Copyists (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Works Performed (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - 1995 Requests Filled (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - May 28 Short repertoire list (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Native American (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Selected Orchestral Music by Women (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - BMI Reports (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Women's Philharmonic List of Performed Works (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Recommended Works (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Reconstruction of repertoire list (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Elinor Armer Concerto (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Carl Fischer contract (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Maud Powell (Violinist from early 1900s) (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Recommended Works reconstructed (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Afro-Am Music and Culture (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Performance "other" for future reference (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Boosey and Hawkes (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Music Schools (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Composers to Research (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Sampler Tape (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Reading Material (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Women's Orchestral Works of the 20th Century: workshop 1997 with audio tapes (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Latinas Catalog and Annotations (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Latin American Women Composers and Compser references (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Theo. Front Music Literature: Women Composers Listings (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Tape Use: signed agreements 1998 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Misc. Performer and Composer Inquiries 1996-1997 (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Music Library Misc. Contact and Publisher INformation (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Librarian Position job description (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Tape Library: j-card materials (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - 1999-2000 piece timings (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Cassette library materials (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Music Library Resources (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Personal Use: Cassette tapes agreement (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - Artistic Committee Planning materials (Box 123, Folder 16)
  - Score Perusal and rental May 8, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 17)
  - Publisher and music Library Correspodence and materials 1993` (Box 123, Folder 18)
  - Score rentals Feb. 6, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 19)
  - August 2, 1992 Library materials (Box 123, Folder 20)
  - Misc. Music Library Transactions Nov. 14, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 21)
  - Music Part Assignments Oct. 3, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 22)
  - Library Rentals: Oct. 16, 1999 (Box 123, Folder 23)
  - 1999-2000 Season and Library materials (Box 123, Folder 24)
  - Brouwer, Margaret: Symphony No. 1 Rental (Box 123, Folder 25)
  - Presser Music Pub. and Music Library materials (Box 123, Folder 26)
  - Rental: Diemer, Emma Lou; Suite of Homages (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Davidson, Tina; They Come Dancing rental materials (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Katharine O'Connell music library correspondence (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Chen Yi: Violin Concerto and library correspondence (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Garrop, Stacy: Thunderwalker; correspondence (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Gould, Morton: Spirituals for Strings; rental materials (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Hairston, Jacq: arrangements (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Hairston, Jacqueline: A Spirituals Trilogy Nov. 24, 2000 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Kohjiba, Tomiko: Transmigration of the Soul (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Kotova, Nina: Cello concerto materials (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Larsen, Libby: Symphony; Water Music materials (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Larsen, Libby: Lost John materials (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Luther, Molly: Variants for Orchestra materials (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - Martines, Marianne: Sinfonia in C materials (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - Rebecca Oswald correspondence (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - Perry, Julia: Short Piece for Orchestra materials (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - Price, Florence: Symp. No.3 in C minor (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - Tann, Hilary: From Afar materials (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - Wagner, Melinda: Concerto for Flute materials (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - Zaimont, Judith Lang: Symph. No. 1 (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - Brouwer, Margaret: Fanfare (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - 1997-1998 Season and music library materials (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - June 8, 1997 Reading Session materials (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - March 29, 1997 Concert materials (Box 124, Folder 24)
  - March 1, 1997 concert materials (Box 124, Folder 25)
  - Jan. 25, 1997 Concert materials (Box 124, Folder 26)
  - Jan. 25, 1997 Concert materials (Box 124, Folder 27)
  - Reading Session Sept. 1996 (Box 124, Folder 28)
  - June 1996 Concert materials (Box 124, Folder 29)
  - 1994-1995 Season and materials (Box 124, Folder 30)
  - Cancelled May 1995 set and music materials (Box 124, Folder 31`)
  - Jan. 28, 1994 Concert materials (Box 124, Folder 32)
  - Music Materials: Nov. 1994 Tour (Box 124, Folder 33)
  - October 1994 music materials (Box 124, Folder 34)
  - May 1994 music (Box 124, Folder 35)
  - Feb. 1994 Music materials (Box 124, Folder 36)
  - January 1994 set (repertoire performed) (Box 124, Folder 37)
  - Nov. 1993 set (repertoire performed) (Box 124, Folder 38)
  - October 1993 Set (repertoire performed) (Box 124, Folder 39)
  - Jan, 23, 1999 music materials (Box 124, Folder 40)
  - Decemebr 10, 1998 "Special Concert" music prep (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Nov. 14, 1998 Concert and music library notes (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Reading Session July 1998 music prep notes (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - May 9 1992 music prep notes (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Library notes March 1992 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Library March 21, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Library Notes Feb. 1, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Library materials and notes Nov. 21/23 1991 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Library notes January 12, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Library notes Oct. 5, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - United Parcel Service and music library materials (Box 125, Folder 31)
  - library notes April 27, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Library notes March 14/21/23, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Library notes Feb. 9, 1991 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Library notes January 1991 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Library notes Nov. 2/3, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Library notes Oct. 6, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - Music library perusal orders 1992 (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - Music rentals and correspondence (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - ASCAP and publisher member materials (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Music Rental Income notes (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence related to rentals (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - Rental requests-music library (Box 125, Folder 22)
  - Marianna Martines "Sinfornia" and information contact July 20, 1999 (Box 125, Folder 23)
  - Past rentals and loans: Boulanger; Kirlin; Aufderheide (Box 125, Folder 24)
  - Music rentals: past (Fanny Mendelssohn only) (Box 125, Folder 25)
  - Florence Price: Symph. #3 materials (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - Fanny Mendelssohn rental history (Box 125, Folder 27)
  - May 28, 1999 concert materials (Box 125, Folder 28)
  - April 1999 library notes (Box 125, Folder 29)
  - Daria D'Andrea (music librarian) correspondence and notes (Box 125, Folder 30)
  - 10 years: Premiers and Commissions (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - List of Works Performed: 1981-2000 (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Overview of Program Repertoire lists, 1993-1997 (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Reconstructions: music scores (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - "The Maud Powell Signature Women in Music," Winter 1996 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - "Women and Music," vol. 1, 1997 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - "Standard Repertoire," Master's Thesis, 1994 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - "Peanuts" cartoon, undated (Box 172, Folder 8)
- Series XIV: Guest Artists
  Guest Artists
  A listing of the various guest artists who performed with the Women's Philharmonic: contracts and correspondence.
  - Agualina, Florence (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Terrie Baune (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Terrie Baune contract 3/10/01 (Box 64, Folder 33)
  - 4/3/93 Victoria Bond; Cynthia Sikes (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Victoria Bond, conductor/ Cynthia Sikes, sax; April 3 1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Bonita Boyd contract 5/13/00 (Box 64, Folder 30)
  - Bonita Boyd (flute) (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Brown, Velvet: contract 10/6/01 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Brown, Velvet (tuba) (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - 11/14/92 Heather Buckman Trombone (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Angela Cheng, Gillian Benet 5/9/92 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - March 10, 2001 Diemer, Foluiile, Chen Yi (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Stacy Garrop (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Guest Artists (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Irma Erman (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Jeanrenaud, Joan: contract 1/26/02 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Kotova, Nina contract 9/30/00 (Box 64, Folder 29)
  - May 6, 1995 Chi-Fun Lee piano (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Mancini, Patricia (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - 10/6/91 Ursula Oppens (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Oppens, Ursula: contract 5/11/02 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Ursula Oppens, Herbst Theater 10/5/91 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Polk, Joanne--piano (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - 10/6/90 Paula Robison (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Feb 11, 1989 Sharon Robinson (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Girls Chorus 3/21/92 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - 3/21/91-3/23/91 Debbie Schwartz (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - April 20, 1990 Susan Slaughter (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Tanaka, Karen: contract 1/26/02 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Linda Tillery + Cultural Heritage (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Tillery + Cultural Heritage Choir 2001 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Tillery + Cultural Heritage Choir Contract 11/24/00 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Mary Jean Van Appledorn (Box 63, Folder 17)